HAEUN SONG

(647) 473-5160 | haeunsong0615@gmail.com | LinkedIn: haeun--song | GitHub: @haeunyy96

PROFILE

I am a web developer with a background in healthcare education and hands-on care. With experiences in working in a fast-paced environment, where multi-tasking, prioritization and teamwork was key, I have a passion to build useful, engaging, and accessible websites and applications.

SKILLS

HTML5 | CSS3 | SCSS | JavaScript (ES6, ES5) | Version Control (Git) | React | JQuery | RESTful API | Node.js | Responsive Designs | Performance Testing | Project Scope Management | Team-based development | Pair programming Teamwork | Leadership | Communication | Facilitation skills | Prioritization

EDUCATION

Juno College of Technology

• Web Development Bootcamp

July 2022 - Present

University of Toronto

• Honours Bachelor of Science, Nursing (BScN)

Sep 2018 – Jun 2020

• Honours Bachelor of Science (BSc); Major Human Biology and Physiology

Sep 2014 – Apr 2018

PROJECTS

Scene It

- An interactive website using RESTful API to search for things to do at different travel destinations.
- Incorporated HTML5, CSS3, SASS, JavaScript and RESTful API to elevate user experience

Bar One

- A multipage-responsive website for promotion of a potential business
- Incorporated HTML5, CSS3, SASS and JavaScript to create an interactive website
- Will enable a business to have a better user-interaction and navigation

Dice Roller

- A simple dice rolling app where two dices are randomly rolled, and a winner is announced.
- Incorporated HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript

PROFESSIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE

University of Toronto | Web Developer

Jan 2023 - Current

Division of Anatomy, Department of Surgery, Faculty of Medicine

• Designing and developing an interactive website for 3D Anatomy viewer for the university.

University of Toronto | Gross Anatomy Lab Demonstrator and Prosector

May 2018 - Current

Division of Anatomy, Department of Surgery, Faculty of Medicine | Faculty of Dentistry

- Supervised full-body cadaveric dissections for professional students with no previous dissection experiences
- Instructed comprehensive anatomy lab sessions for medical, dental and physiotherapy students
- Created 500+ dissections and plastination of cadavers for use with various anatomy courses at the university

The Hospital for Sick Children (SickKids) | Registered Nurse

Aug 2020 - Aug 2021

8C: Burns, Plastic Surgery, Urology and Ophthalmology Unit

- Provided client experience through care plan creation with several stake holders (doctors, pharmacists, and social workers) tailored individually for each patient.
- Supported 500+ patients' hospitalization journey from pre-admission to discharge by providing compassionate care for patients and families and incorporating understanding of different social determinants of health

Sunnybrook Health Sciences Centre | Clinical Extern

June 2019 - July 2020

D3: Cardiology and Cardiovascular Surgery Unit & D7: Burns Intensive Care Unit (ICU)

- Demonstrated prioritization and time management skills whilst providing direct care to pre-operative and post-operative patients under mentorship and supervision of registered nurses.
- Provided psychosocial support for patients and families and communicated as a bridge between patients and the interprofessional team on unit.